Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Rose, Jessie W., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 220)
  Correspondence with Jessie W. Rose of Pittsburgh, PA. The only grandchild of SCF, Mrs. Rose and her mother, Marion Welch (sometimes Welsh) were contacted by Lilly soon after he began his collection. The family was poor and happy to sell some of Foster's most important belongings, but they were interested only in profit. In addition, there was a great deal of disharmony between various branches of the family, and this bitterness runs throughout the correspondence. Lilly remained on polite, if cool terms with them because of their value as direct descendants. The file gives insight on many of the people important to the development of the collection. Mrs. Rose was a great gossiper, and while her information was not always correct, it was certainly interesting.
- RI RO RU RY, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  Correspondence with George M. Robinson; Lucien Rule; Rutgers University Library; Richmond Public Library; Riverside Public Library; Roanoke Public Library; L.H.S. Robson; Charles Ridinger; Frank S. Ruddle; Henry T. Richards; Jules T. Richards; Sterling Russell; Mildred Romfh; William Richardson; Frank Ruddell; Frances Richards; Fred Rouleau; Wells Rupert; Royal Typewriter Company Inc.; Robson & Howgate; Sidney Rose; Cale Young Rice; Anthony Russo; Arthur Rutledge; W.M. Rider; Women's Rotary Club of Indianapolis; Riverside School; Foster W. Rice; A.C. Robinson; Alexander Robinson; Charles W. Ridinger; Dallmeyer Russell; David Ross; Ben Roth; Rosenbach Company
- SA SC, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  Correspondence with Julian Schmitz; W. Saunders; E.S. Schilling; Margaret Scott; San Diego Public Library; San Francisco Public Library; Mary Schneider; Nora Schwab; Louise Scudder; Ella Sengenberger; W. Saunders; Gerry Sanborn; George Schwartz; Arthur Schomberg; Rossing Sardeson; Antonia Sawyer; Mary Schneider; Scottish Musical Magazine; Henry Schauffler; Henry Scholl; G. Schirmer Inc.; C.H. Schwomeyer; Lorenz Schumm; William Saltmarsh; S.I. Sayre; Frank Scopes; Walter Schaefer; Thomas W. Schreiner; Ferdinand Schaeffer; Townley Searle
- Searle, Townley, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  Correspondence with Townley Searle, a London based author compiling a book of old music hall songs. He wrote to Foster Hall for info on SCF and then began to supply Lilly with British editions of Foster music and songbooks
- SE SH, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  Correspondence with Second Presbyterian Church; Robert Shackleton; George Shiras; Myra Siviter; Helen Marott Sinex; Shelbyville Public Library; Sears Roebuck Co.; Regis Sieffert; O.P. Shiras; Seven Bookhunters; H.M. Sender; Shortridge High School; H.M. Sender; Shapiro Berstein & Co.; Elliot Shapiro; Shepard Book Co.; City of Sheffield Public Libraries; Margaret Sherman
- SI SK, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  Correspondence with Simmons College Library; Arthur Siviter; G.M. Sieffert; John Skinner; Frederick Woodward Skiff; H.D. Sickles
- SL SM SN SQ, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  Correspondence with Leora Smith; Florence Smith; Eleanor Smith; Southern Methodist University; J. Marsh Spafford; University of South Dakota; Fred Harlow Smith; Smith Book Company; F.J. Snyder; Will H. Solle; Nelly Colfax Smith; Dana P. Smith; Southern Baptist Theological Seminary; C.D. Smith; University College Southampton; Ralph Fisher Smith; Barbara Sprague; J.E. Spannuth; H. Goodwin Spaulding; Francis Edgar Smith; Eva P. Squires; Mildren Rohm Smith; Public Library of the City of Somerville; Kate Smith; William Watson Smith; Southern Club Auxiliary; James Spencer; Lois Snyder; Smith College; Public Library South Bend; F. Vernon Smith; E.D. Sloan
- Smith, Percy, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  Correspondence with Percy Smith of St. Louis, MO, Publisher of Morrison's biography of Stephen. Over the course of three years he sent Foster Hall a steady stream of reminiscences, repeating stories Morrison had told him thirty years earlier.
- Smythe, Arthur H., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 228)
- ST SU SW SY, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  Correspondence with Sugarloaf Historical Association; Forest Sweet; Stanford University Libraries; C.H. Stocking; Helen K. Starr; Raymond Stites; Syracuse Public Library; Virgil T. Stone; Library of Swarthmore College; J.W. Sturmer; Elmer Steffen; Ebora Strong; Albert Stackman; Forest Sweet; Scion Stagg; William Stevens; Star Publishing Co.; W.K. Stewart Co.; Malcolm Stone; Forest H. Sweet; Charles Messer Stow; Emero Stiegman; Standard Publishing Company; Kentucky Standard; Burton Stevenson; P. Stammer; State Savings and Loan Association; C.V. Starrett; Eleanor Stimmel; O.W. Stephenson; E.R. Stilson; Louis Clyde Stoumen; James Stewart; Frances Stiver; Roy Strayer; Stewart Kidd; W.W. Starkey; St. Mary's Home for Children; Guy Stonestreet; St. Louis Public Library
- T, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  Correspondence with L.W. Trager; Wilfred Thomas; Thomas Taylor; Irene Tilyard; James C. Tait; William Tutin; Toledo Public Library; State of Tennessee Department of Education; Public Library of Toronto; A.B. Tryke; Tulsa Public Library; M.L. Turtelot; Lewis McKenzie Turner; Mary Talor; John Thompson; Anna Tenney; Texas State College for Women; Tipton Musicals; Isabel Lewis Townsend; Maggie Taylor; C.S. Thomas; Georguen Ter-Sarkissian; C.E. Bushong; Rees M. Ryan; John Lloyd Weller; Isabel Townsend; Stella Weiler Taylor; Julian Treilhard; Tipton Public Library; Ticknor Club; Eloise Thomas; Carl Tollefsen; Trinity Cathedral; Ada Toft; Tuttle Company; R.C. Ballard Thruston; George W. Ternes; Thatcher's Old Book Shop; H.C. Tillson; Robert Norwood Taylor; University of Texas; W.E. Treanor; Tennessee State Library; Edward Turnball; Tufts College; Troy Public Library; Transylvania Printing Co.; Tams-Witmark Music Library Inc.; Mary Lyon Taylor
- Thayer, Mary Alden, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  Correspondence with Mary Alden Thayer, a librarian at the New England Conservatory of Music. She sold some sheet music to Lilly, but he later refused to buy from her. There are hints that the material she sold was stolen.
- Townsend, John Wilson, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 232)
- UV, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 233)
  Correspondence with United States Naval Academy; Vineland Historical and Antiquarian Society; Librarian at the University of Virginia; Vermont Historical Society; C.W. Unger; Vassar College Library; C.E. Van Norman; A.M. Uhler; Utica Public Library; Home Economics Club of Valley HIlls; Virginia Historical Society; Van Ulier; Indiana Vassar Club; Irving Van Vliet; William Treat Upton; Alfred Uhler; John Vretos; Robert Vaughan; Betty Veyssie; R.S. Van Loon; F.B. Vesper, Jr.; Vandaworker Club; Veterans Administration; Veterans Hospital; Virginia State Library; Vanderbilt University; Guernsey Van Riper; Sidener Van Riper & Keeling Advertising; University Club
- WA WE, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 234)
  Correspondence with Western Kentucky State Teacher's College; Paul Wagner; I Warshaw; John Walker; Jack Walker; Western Reserve University; Western Reserve Historical Society; Western College Alumnae Group; Western Union; Nellie Wells; Naomi Webb; Mary Watson; A.S. Wathen; J.R. Weldin; E.J. Wessen; Gertrude Perry West; Marion Foster Welch; Gabriel Wells; Edgar S. Werner; Lawrence James Wathen; Wellesley College; West Virginia University; Wabash College Library; Oscar Wegelin; Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania; Western Reserve Historical Society; Dr. E.R. Weidlein; Watkinson Library; W.F.B..
- WH WI, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 235)
  Correspondence with Warner Williams; Camilla Whitcomb; Whitlock's Book Store; Elizabeth Tenney Wilson; Amelia White; Wilder's Bookshop; Wigan Public Libraries; Windsor Library Association; Eilie Wilcox; Whitehead & Hoag Company; A. Wiegand's Sons Company; Alice Logan Wingo; Rev. John C. Wingering; Bjorn Winger; Wilson & Harrison; WJR Goodwill Station; WKBF Radio Station; Samuel W. Wilson; Walter L. White; George R. Williams; J.H. Whitty; J.M. Wise; M.D. Wilt; Howard Wiley; Joseph S. Willard; State Historical Society of Wisconsin; Harry Wheatley; Rev. John C.Wingering; Carl Wittke; Ernest William Winkler; Whiting Public Library; Harriet Williams; Anna W. Wheless
- Whittlesey, W.R., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 236)
  Correspondence with Walter Whittlesey of Washington DC. Whittlesey was an employee of the Library of Congress. His initial contacts with Lilly consisted of answering various questions from the Foster Hall staff. IN 1932 he was forced to retire from the Library, but because by that time he was engaged in research for Lilly he was allowed to maintain a desk there and continue his work. After his retirement, Lilly began paying him a monthly allowance. Whittlesey's work was to aid in the systematic coordination of Lilly's collection, verification of facts (copyright, etc.), checking over the reproductions for flaws, assisting E.F. Morneweck in the writing of The Chronicles, mounting such ephemeral material as newspaper clippings, and so on. In short, his high degree of professionalism made him invaluable to the development of the collection. When he died in 1936, his daughter (Katherine Copley), who was already assisting him, remained in Lilly's employment and continued her father's work.
- Wilson, Mary A., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 237)
  Correspondence with Mary Wilson of Indianapolis, In [see also Johnson, Mary E.] Wilson was one of two disabled typists employed by the hall. After the Collection was moved to Pittsburgh she continued to work for Mr. Hodges long distance. Among other tasks she helped to type Mrs. Morneweck's manuscript of The Chronicles.
- WO WR WU WY, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 238)
  Correspondence with Nanno Woods; Edith Wright; Dr. Perry Worden; E. Jay Wholgemuth; Women's Department Club; E.J. Wotowa; C.W. Wynn; Florence Woodward; Women's Press; Free Public Library Worcester; Wyoming Historical and Geological Society; Minne Wynne; Woodlawn Bookshop; Women's Rotary Club
- XYZ, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 239)
  Correspondence with Youngstown Public Library; Public Library York; Frank P. York; Yale University; L.G. Zerfas; Lewis E. Young; Otto Zimmerman & Son Co.; Ye Old Book Shoppe; Young Women's Christian Association Library
- A, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 240)
  Correspondence with Mary F. Allgauer; Atlantic Monthly; Walter Atkins; Associated Coin & Stamp Co.; American Book Co.; Mary E. Armington; M.F.. Allgauer; L.S. Ayres & Co.; Alpha Kappa Latreian; D. Appleton-Century Co.; C.W. Allyn; Aldine Book Co.; All Saints Cathedral; Robert Alexander; A. A. U. W.; Franklin Adams; Baldwin Allan-Allen; Henry Armstrong; Arsenal Technical High School; Altrusa Club; Ashtabula Public Library; Asbury Park Public Library; Artcraft Lithograph & Printing Co.; Alexandria Public Library; Carnegie Public Library Austin, MN; Arcane Book Shop; Fannie Aiken; Frank Forrestall Adams; American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers; Alexander Mitchell Library; American Federation of Musicians; L.S. Ayres & Co.; Carnegie Library, Anniston AL; Carnegie Library Americus, GA; Carnegie Library Akron, IN; Arizona; Allen's Bookstore Inc.; American Association of Museums; Appalachian Journal; Eckhart Public Library Auburn, IN; Crosby Adams; State of Arkansas Dept. of Education; B.J. Jones Memorial Library Akron, OH; W.M. Andrews; WJW Incorporated Akron OH; Anderson Broadcasting Corp; Southern Broadcasting Stations Inc. Atlanta, GA; KXRO Aberdeen, WA; Allegheny College; Radio Station KNOW Austin; Jones Library Amherst, MA; Ashland Public Library; Aurand's Book Store; Harold Arnholter; Art Publication Society; City of Atlanta; Dept. of Archives and History Montgomery Alabama; Alhamra City High School; American Manufacturers Export Association; Arhtur Allen; American News Trade Journal; Library and Museum Juneau Alaska; Martha Allen; Potter County Free Library Amarillo TX; Ashland Library; Ethel V. Anne; Young E. Allison Jr.; Alameda High School; Amicitia Club; Charles F. Alker; Allentown Free Library; Auburn Public Library; Alfred University; Anderson Carnegie Public Library; Alpha Gama Delta Club; Aurora College; Altrusa Club; American Academy of Arts and Letters; Margaret Agnew; Charles Alker; Sue Artis; Atlanta Art Association; Altoona School District; Public Library Ann Arbor MI
- Alwes, Gladys, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 241)
- American Library Service, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 242)
  Correspondence with American Library Service of New York, NY [see also New York Library Service]. ALS was a company of dealers who did not contact Lilly until 1934. At that time they attempted to sell him publications produced by Foster Hall.
- BA, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 243)
  Correspondence with William H. Ball; Ball Brothers Co.; Emma Bates; Maurice Baron; Baldwin-Wallace College; Ball State Teacher's College; Baltimore Public Library; Vivian Barnes; Metropolitan Borough of Battersea; Babson Park, MA; WCAO Baltimore; Bakersfield; Marion Barker; Walter Barnwell; Everett Baker; G.A. Baker & Co. Inc.; Free Public Library of Boyonne, NJ; Barabook Public Library; Peabody Institute Baltimore; Paul Bayless; Bay City Public Library; John Ballentine; E.P. Barmore; Gertrude Brandes; Bartholomew County Historical Society; Baylor University Library; Robert Burns Bair; Bangor Public Library
- BE, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 244)
  Correspondence with Beique Rare Books Service; Martha Beman; Bellevue-Stratford; Beverlry, MA; Vivan Beaumont; Ernest Beique; Irving Berlin; Mary Miller Beard; Frank Bender Bookseller; Carnegie Library Beaver Falls; Dr. William Jesse Baird; Berea College; Bemidji Public Library; Bedford Public Library; Linda Berry; Stanley Bezanson; Walter Beavans; Beloit College; John Beaty; Bethlehem Public Library; Agnes Bedell; Berry schools; Belleville Public Library; J.C. Beckam; Berkeley Public Library; Iva M. Butlin; Howard Bement; Pearl Agnes Beal; Carl Bernhardt; John H. Beck; Beaumont, TX, Torrell Public LIbrary; Public Library Bellingham WA; Cara Foster Beach; Berwyn Public Library; Marguerite Bennetll
- BI BL BO, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  Correspondence with Grace Boyce; R.R. Bowker Co.; Albert Bieber; Book Club; Parmly Billings Memorial Library; Booklover's Shop; Boston Public Library; Ann Boody; Boston Antique Shop; John Black; Jacob Blanck; Florence Boyd; Blue Mountain College; Blue Earth, MN; Black Hawk; Book Den; Bok Singing Tower; Clara Black; Binghampton, NY; Huse Blomburg; Billings, Montana; C.S. Boyd; NBC Boston; Dorothy Black; Birmingham, AL; Bluffton, IN; F.J. Boerger; Carnegie Library Boise Idaho; Book Nook; Misses Binford; John A. Borrows; Mabel Barnum; Boston College; E.A. Blank; Public Library of Bloomfield, NJ: Louis Block; Bowdoin College Library; Boston Athenaeum; Birmingham Conservatory of Music Inc.; Boston Music Co.
- Birge, Mr. & Mrs. Edward B., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  Correspondence with Mr. and Mrs. Edward B. Birge. Edward Birge, a Professor of music at Indiana University, worked with Will Earhart on The Songs of Stephen Foster, a songbook published by University of Pittsbugh Press.
- BR, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  Correspondence with Blanche Bruton; Charles Bragin; Janet Bradley; Bradford, PA, Carnegie Library; Josephine Bruce; Irving Brown; Brooklyn College; Robert Brooke; Bryan, TX, Carnegie Library; Brainerd, MN, Public Library; Cornelia Brooke; W.L. Brown; British Broadcasting Co.; Brookville, IN, Public Library; Captain Taylor Branson; Brown & Bigelow; George A. Brown; E.K. Braselton; H.G. Brannen; Eleanor Browning; Roert Barton; Peter Brannon; British Museum; Bradford County Historical Society; Albert Brush; Bryn Mawr College; Brown University; University of Bristol; Broadway Works Class; Sedley Brown; Estella Briggs; Brushy Mountain Penitentiary; Arthur Brown; Public Library of Brookline; Brigham Young University; Leonard Bryan; Bridgeport Public Library
- Briggs, Morris H., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 248)
- Butterfield, Henry, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  Correspondence with Henry Butterfield of Brookline, MA. A descendent of Stephen's brother Henry, Mr. Butterfield sold Lilly two volumes of sheet music which had been handed down through the family for $850. After this successful sale, Butterfield attempted to sell old clothing belonging to the Foster family.
- BU BY, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  Correspondence with Buffalo, NY; Bertha C. Burhans; Jay G. Buchan; Butler Public Library; Carl Busch; C.S. Boyd; Buffalo Evening News; Amos W. Butler; Buffalo Catholic Institute Library; Grosvenor Library Buffalo; Women's Literary Club of Bunker Hill; Arthur E. Byrne; Donald Q. Burleigh; Sunoule Butler; Burlett Club; Free Public Library Burlington; Buriett Club; Sarah D. Butler; University of Buffalo; Butler University
- CA CE, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 251)
  Correspondence with Charles Capron; Arthur Carlson; Century Paper Company; Central Missouri State Teachers College; Nan Cartwright; Hotel Chelsea; Central Society of Scientists and Mathematicians; Cairo Public Library; Harry Campbell; Gayle Carver; Casper Public Library; Cambridge Public Library; Canal Zone Schools; Tudor B. Carre; Central Park Public Library; Camden Free Public Library; Frank Carpenter; Maurice Candey; Centre College; Carthage College; Catawba College; University Library Cambridge; Catholic University of America; Ruth Cazier; John Carroll University; Wallace Cain; Russell Case; Carnegie Institute of Technology; Camp Fire Girls; California State Library; Frances Soule Campbell; Canton Public Library Association; University of California
- Callahan, Lorena (Lott), 1934 (Box 9, Folder 252)
  Correspondence with Lorena Calahan of Louisville, KY. Not a dealer, but as a life-long resident of Louisville she was acquainted with many of the old families there, and obtained sheet music from them. Her letters are like full-length novels and she sounds quite mad. Over the years she developed a crush on Lilly and continued to write even after her flurry of sales dwindled away. The file for 1933 contains some interested gossip about Col. La Bree. Mrs. Lott insinuates he stole a good deal of sheet music and other items from the MOKH museum. When Lilly remarried in 1935, Mrs. Lott turned her affections to Mr. Hodges.
- Certain, Mrs. Henry J., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 253)
  Correspondence of Mrs. Henry J. Certain of Huntsville, AL. From 1931 on Mrs. Certain was one of the main suppliers of sheet music to Foster Hall. Her prices were always reasonable, and her material in good condition. Lilly so respected her business-like attitude and high standards that she was one of his personal guests at the dedication ceremonies in Pittsburgh.
- CH CI CL CO, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  Correspondence with David Costelo; William H. Conroy; L.S. Clark; F. Christopher; Stuart Conroy; E. Fred Chanay; Carnegie Public Library Charleston; Chesapeake and Ohio Lines; George H. Clark; E. Fred Chaney; George W. Childs; Frank S. Collins; H.O. Bishop; Stanley Coulter; James E. Clark; Frank S. Collins; Colophon; George Childs; W.R. Conrad; G.H. Cordell; Werner R. Conrad; Clarksdale Carnegie Public Library; Wayne Coy; Coleraine Publi Library; Clearwater Public Library; George S. Cottoman; Alvin T. Coate; P.W. Coris; Congregational Church; Chillicothe; Coshocton Public Library; Connellsville Carnegie Library; Corsicana Public Library; John. R. Clements; Clearwater Public Library; Columbia University; Palmer Clark; John Lyle Clough; Cleveland Public Library; Frank S. Collins; Clear Lake City Library; A.T. Copeland; Community Broadcast Corporation Charlottesville; KFRU Columbia, MO: Eugene Connelly; Corydon Public Library; George H. Cooper; Robert Cooke; William Kenneth Collette; WKRC Cincinnati; WCHS Charleston; WIS Columia; Alfred Cobley; L.M. Christian; R.G. Clifton; Chattanooga Public Library; Claremont College; Cisco Texas; J. Winston Coleman, Jr.; A.D. Coolbaugh; Richard C. Collins; Connecticut College; Le Retama Public Library Corpus Christi; Cleveland Heights Public Library; George Clark; Colorado College; Children's Museum of Indianapolis; David Costelo; City of Clifton; Walter Cluff; J.S. Chambers; Columbus Bartholomew County Library; Converse College Library; Cecilia Charles; Public Library of Concord; Montgomery Cooper; Edgar Cowan; Clinton Public Library; Hugh Constable; Cole's Arcade; Florence Cochran; Scott Chambers; Carnegie Public Library Cheyenne; Nora Crimmins
- Chicago, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  Correspondence with Letters from librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations in the Chicago area thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications
- Cincinnati, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  Letters from librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations in Cincinnati thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications
- Conn, Mrs. Louella C., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Louella C. Conn of Dayton, OH. With Lilly supplying the funding, Mrs. Conn directed the recording of each of Foster's tunes on the Gennett Record label. These Foster Hall Recordings were not for public sale; they were solely for use by the Hall. Recording was completed in 1936. Mrs. Conn was responsible for identifying that several of Foster's tunes consisted of different words set to the same air.
- CR CY CU, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  Correspondence with Crescent Paper Company; Drusilla Cravens; Harold R. Cunning; Warren Weston Creamer; Carnegie Public Library Crookston; Current Knowledge Club; Crescent Hill Women's Club; Cecilia Todd Cross; W.D. Crooks; Culver-Stockton College; L.G. Crume; Curtis Institute of Music; Crozer Theological Seminary; L.G. Crume; Crist Book Shop; Gladys Cranmer; Crist Book Shop; Creighton University; Cumberland University Alumni Association; H.J. Craig
- Crowell, Thomas Y. Company, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  Correspondence with the Thomas Y. Crowell Company of NY, NY. This was the company that published Howard's biography of Foster. Because Lilly had subsidized Howard during his research, he also had a great deal of say over the final form of the book. Lilly and Crowell wrangle over the title and against Howard's wish changed it from Dear Friends and Gentle Hearts to America's Troubadour.
- DA DE, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 260)
  Correspondence with W.H. Davis; S. Foster Damon; Delta Alpha Gamma; Martha Davis; Ruth Denton; J.E. Deaver; Ed DeCamp; S.O. Davidson; Henry B. Davis; Denmark; May Davis; Danville Friends Church; Daughters of the American Revolution; Danbury Library; F.B. Davenport; Central Broadcasting Company Des Moines; Ernest Dawkins; Norma Death; Decatur Public Library; Danville Music Club; Carnegie Library Drivis Lake; Carnegie Library Detroit Lakes; WJBK Detroit; WMBC Detroit; Detroit Public LIbrary; Kirk Delano; KFXF Denver; Fordson Board of Education Dearborn; Margaret Daschbah; KRLD Dallas; Dayton Public Library; Goodwill Station Detroit; University of Detroit; Dartmouth College; Carolyn Darrow; Grover Tilden Davis; Historical Society of Delaware; University of Denver Library; Judge Frank E. Daugherty; Claire Dardis; Francis May Davis; Dakota Wesleyan University; Dana's Musical Institute; Lynn B. Dana; J.E. DeGafferelly; Denison University; Davis and Elkins College News Bureau; DePauw University; Margaret Daschbach; Denison University Library
- Daniel, Mrs. Kathryn, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 261)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Kathryn Daniel of Ancot, CZ. A school teacher working in the Canal Zone, Mrs. Daniels first wrote to tell Lilly about a play she staged at her school. The play, a dramatized biography of Foster, was entitled Stephen Foster: A Reminiscence. Impressed with both the woman and the play, Lilly sponsored the financial side of its publication.
- DI DO DR DY, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 262)